A Guide to the Papers of Julian Bond, 1897-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Articles and Speeches by Julian Bond
  - Speech delivered at the NAACP's Annual Meeting, 2001 February 17 (Box-folder 10:14)
  - Speech delivered at the 92nd Annual NAACP Convention, Ernest N. Morial Convention Center, New Orleans, Louisiana, 2001 July 8 (Box-folder 10:15)
  - Speech concerning the National Housing Act of 1949 and the continued need for fair housing delivered at the Ethel Lawrence Homes Dedication, Mount Laurel, New Jersey, 2001 September 15 (Box-folder 10:16)
  - Speech concerning slaves and their legacy delivered at Monticello, Albemarle County, Virginia, 2001 October 6 (Box-folder 10:17)
  - Speech concerning the relationship of the NAACP and the series of Presidents during their 92 year history, 2001 (Box-folder 10:18)
  - Speech concerning Diversity, 2001 (Box-folder 10:19)
  - Speech- Public Intellectuals, 2002 April 12 (Box-folder 10:20)
  - Speech delivered at the National Baptist Convention, USA, concerning the faith of African-Americans and the Civil Rights Movement, [2002 June?] (Box-folder 10:21)
  - Speech delivered at the NAACP Convention, George Brown Convention Center, Houston, Texas, 2002 July 7 (Box-folder 10:22)
  - Speech delivered at the University of Virginia Anti-war Rally, 2002 November 20 (Box-folder 10:23)
  - Article- Relic of Past Overstayed His Welcome concerning Strom Thurmond of South Carolina, 2002 December 5 (Box-folder 10:24)
  - Speech concerning affirmative action, 2002 (Box-folder 10:25)
  - Speech concerning the role of civil rights organizations in today's racial climate, 2002 (Box-folder 10:26)
  - Speech delivered at the 2003 NAACP Convention, Miami, Florida, 2003 July 13 (Box-folder 10:27)
  - Speech concerning James Bond for Berea College Founder's Day, Berea College, Kentucky, 2003 October 10 (Box-folder 10:28)
  - Speech- SNCC: What We Did with corrections, additions, and annotations, 2003 (Box-folder 10:29)
  - Speech before lawyers about his experiences in the judicial system, 2003 (Box-folder 10:30)
  - Speech concerning the practice of law and its inequities, 2003 (Box-folder 10:31)
  - Speech- Acting Affirmatively, 2003 (Box-folder 10:32)
  - Speech delivered at the National Abortion Rights Action League concerning Roe v Wade 31st Anniversary, 2004 January 22 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Speech delivered to the 2004 NAACP Convention, Philadelphia Convention Center, Pennsylvania, 2004 July 11 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Speech- The Broken Promise of 'Brown v Board of Education' with Research Material, 2004 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Speech concerning the American Civil Liberties Union, Earl Warren, and Race in American politics, 2004 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Speech- The 1965 Voting Rights Act, A Beneficiary's Perspective, 2004 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Speech delivered at [Lincoln University ?], 2004 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Speech- Campaign for America's Future, 2004 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Speech delivered before the Florida State branch of the NAACP, ca. 2004 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Speech delivered at the NAACP Annual Meeting, 2005 February 19 (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Speech accepting the Hubert Humphrey Award at the Leadership Conference on Civil Rights Dinner, 2005 May 4 (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Speech accepting the award at the 2005 Human Rights Campaign Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2005 October 1 (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Speech concerning the crisis in black schools, n.d. (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Speech delivered to the Congress of African People, Atlanta, Georgia, n.d. (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Commencement Address delivered to Columbia University Journalism School, n.d. (Box-folder 11:14)
  - Paper/Speech concerning the Necessity of Communication, Closeness, and Togetherness Among Black People, n.d. (Box-folder 11:15)
  - Speech concerning blacks engaging in a new politics (miscellaneous version, some incomplete), n.d. (Box-folder 11:16)
  - Speech concerning housing and urban development: Congressional Black Caucus' series of recommendations to President Nixon, n.d. (Box-folder 11:17)
  - Speech concerning hunger and malnutrition in the United States, n.d. (Box-folder 11:18)
  - Speech concerning juvenile delinquency, n.d. (Box-folder 11:19)
  - Speech concerning the Legal Defense Fund, the legal arm of the movement, n.d. (Box-folder 11:20)
  - Speech concerning mass participation in Civil Rights Movement, n.d. (Box-folder 11:21)
  - Speech concerning the commitment of the NAACP to an Interracial democracy (draft for Myrlie Evers-Williams), n.d. (Box-folder 11:22)
  - Speech concerning politics and the debate surrounding welfare programs, n.d. (Box-folder 11:23)
  - Speech concerning new faces in Washington conditions for poor black people, n.d. (Box-folder 11:24)
  - Speech concerning the black college: its effect upon black people and opportunity, n.d. (Box-folder 11:25)
  - Speech concerning Civil Rights Movement overview, n.d. (Box-folder 11:26)
  - Speech concerning the crisis facing black schools, n.d. (Box-folder 11:27)
  - Speech concerning the role of the university, n.d. (Box-folder 11:28)
  - Speech- Today's Youth Tomorrow's Leaders, n.d. (Box-folder 11:29)
  - Speech concerning welfare initiatives for minorities, n.d. (Box-folder 11:30)
  - Article Are Gay Rights Civil Rights? in Ebony, n.d. (Box-folder 11:31)
  - Article concerning the need for a Network for Black Issues in Players Magazine, n.d. (Box-folder 11:32)
  - Article on Atlanta and the new South, n.d. (Box-folder 11:33)
  - Speech-Passing the Torch?, n.d. (Box-folder 11:34)
  - [Article?]- James Forman, n.d. (Box-folder 11:35)
  - Article- Politics Makes a Difference in Southern Exposure, n.d. (Box-folder 11:36)
  - Speech- Majority Rule and Black Rights, n.d. (Box-folder 11:37)
  - Speeches- Incomplete, n.d. (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Speech File Material, 1945-1976 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Speech File Material, n.d. (Box-folder 12:3)
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1967 February 3-14 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Correspondence, February 15-29 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Correspondence, 1967 March (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Correspondence, 1967 April-May (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Correspondence, 1967 June (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Correspondence, 1967 July (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Correspondence, 1967 August-December (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 January-February (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Correspondence, 1968 March-May (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Correspondence, 1968 June-July (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Correspondence, 1968 September (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Correspondence, 1968 October 1-21 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Correspondence, 1968 October 22-November (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Correspondence, 1968 December (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Correspondence, 1969 February-September (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Correspondence, 1969 October (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Correspondence, 1969 November (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Correspondence, 1969 December (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Correspondence, 1970 January (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Correspondence, 1970 February (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Correspondence, 1970 March (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Correspondence, 1970 April-May (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Correspondence, 1970 June-July (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Correspondence, 1970 August-September (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Correspondence, 1970 October-December (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Correspondence, 1971 January-February (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Correspondence, 1971 March-May (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Correspondence, 1971 June-July (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Correspondence, 1971 August-September (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Correspondence, 1971 October-December (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Correspondence, 1972 January-March (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Correspondence, 1972 April-May (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Correspondence, 1972 June-July (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Correspondence, 1972 August-September (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Correspondence, 1972 October-December (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Correspondence, 1973 January (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Correspondence, 1973 July (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Correspondence, 1973 September-December (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Correspondence, 1974 January (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Correspondence, 1974 February-1-15 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Correspondence, 1974 February 20-28 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Correspondence, 1974 March (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Correspondence, 1974 April 1-17 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Correspondence, 1974 April 17-30 (Box-folder 17:8)
  - Correspondence, 1974 May 1-20 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Correspondence, 1974 May 21-31 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Correspondence, 1974 June (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Correspondence, 1974 July (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Correspondence, 1974 September (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Correspondence, 1974 October-December (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Correspondence, 1975 January (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Correspondence, 1975 February (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Correspondence, 1975 March (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Correspondence, 1975 April (Box-folder 18:10)
  - Correspondence, 1975 May (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 June (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Correspondence, 1975 July (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Correspondence, 1975 August (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Correspondence, 1975 September (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Correspondence, 1975 October (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Correspondence, 1975 November (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Correspondence, 1975 December (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Correspondence, 1976 January (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Correspondence, 1976 February (Box-folder 19:10)
  - Correspondence, 1976 March (Box-folder 19:11)
  - Correspondence, 1976 April (Box-folder 19:12)
  - Correspondence, 1976 May (Box-folder 19:13)
  - Correspondence, 1976 June (Box-folder 19:14)
  - Correspondence, 1976 July (Box-folder 19:15)
  - Correspondence, 1976 August (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Correspondence, 1976 September (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Correspondence, 1976 October (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Correspondence, 1976 November (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Correspondence, 1976 December (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Correspondence, 1977 Jan (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 February (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Correspondence, 1977 March (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Correspondence, 1977 April (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Correspondence, 1977 May (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Correspondence, 1977 June (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Correspondence, 1977 July (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Correspondence, 1977 August (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Correspondence, 1977 September (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Correspondence- Derogatory Letters, ca. 1969-79, 1988 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1967 December (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1968 January-August (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1968 September 1-10 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1968 September 11-30, n.d. (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1968 October (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1968 November-December (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 January-February (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 March (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 April (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 May (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 June-August (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 September-October (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 November (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1969 December (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 January (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 February (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 March-April (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 May (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 June-July (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 August-September (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 October-November (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 December (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1970 January (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 February-March (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 April (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 May (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 June (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 July (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 August (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 September (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 October (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 November 1-19 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1971 November 21-December (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1972 January -July (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1972 August-September (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1972 October-December (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 January (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 February 1-11 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 February 12-28 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 March-April (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 May (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 June (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 July (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 August-September (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 October (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1973 November-December (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1974 March 1-15 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1974 March 16-31 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1974 May (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1975 January-September (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 January-May (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 June (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 July (Box-folder 27:9)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 August (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 September (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 October (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1976 November-December (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1977 January-February (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1977 March-April (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1977 May (Box-folder 28:7)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, 1977 June-November (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Correspondence- General Requests, n.d. (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- "A" through "E", 1961, 1967-2004 (Box-folder 29:2)
    Correspondents include: Archie E. Allen, Imamu Amiri Baraka (LeRoi Jones), Dan Bernstein, Kay Boyle, Carol Moseley Braun, Justice Stephen Breyer, Erin Brockovich-Ellis, Stokeley Carmichael (Kwame Ture), Georgia Senator Hugh Carter, Linda Chavez-Thompson, Representative Shirley Chisholm, Senator Max Cleland, William Cohen, John Conyers, Jr., W.E.B. Du Bois (autographed program), Governor Michael F. Easley, Senator John Edwards, and Myrlie Evers-Williams.
  - Correspondence- Individuals- "F" through "K", 1960-2004 (Box-folder 29:3)
    Correspondents include: James Farmer, Senator Russell D.Feingold, David Franklin, June Franklin, Dr. John K. Fryer, Nikki Giovanni, Governor Parris N. Glendening, Senator Philip A. Hart, Chester Hartman, Jesse Jackson (autographed speech), Mayor Maynard Jackson, Senator Jacob K. Javits, Vernon E. Jordan, Jr., and Senator John Kerry
  - Correspondence- Individuals- "L" through "W", 1964-2004 (Box-folder 29:4)
    Correspondents include: John Lewis, Walter F. Mondale, Elijah Muhammad (Messenger of Allah, Nation of Islam), Jeff Nesmith, Senator Sam Nunn, Huey P. Newton (Black Panther Party), Adam Clayton Powell, Ann Richards (autographed keynote address for the 1988 Democratic Convention), Donald Rumsfeld, Senator Richard B. Russell, Timothy J. Russert (NBC News), Ken Salazar, Senator Paul S. Sarbanes, Bishop Paul L. Seitz, Secretary of Transportation Rodney E. Slater, Representative Louis Stokes, Percy Sutton, Senator Strom Thurmond, Ahmed Sekou Toure, Representative Morris K. Udall, Governor George C. Wallace, Roy Wilkins (NAACP), and Oprah Winfrey.
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Clarence Avant, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Richard W. Bruner, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- President Bill Clinton, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Ivanhoe Donaldson, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29:8)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Bert Gilden, 1969, 1970 (Box-folder 29:9)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Mayor Richard Hatcher, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 29:10)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Parker Hudson, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 29:11)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Hubert H. Humphrey, 1968 July 10, 11 (Box-folder 29:12)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Kivie Kaplan, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 29:13)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Senator Edward M. Kennedy, 1968-1998 (Box-folder 29:14)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Ethel S. Kennedy, including a photograph of Robert Kennedy, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 29:15)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Coretta Scott King, 1970, 1989 (Box-folder 29:16)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Senator George McGovern, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 29:17)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Sam Massell, 1969 (Box-folder 29:18)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Attorney Howard Moore, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 29:19)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Charles J. Negaro, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 29:20)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Johnny E. Parham, Jr. (Curber Associates, Inc.), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29:21)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- David Pearson (Associates), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29:22)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Donald O. Peterson, 1969 (Box-folder 29:23)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Rosser Reeves, 1969 (Box-folder 29:24)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Mayor Carl B. Stokes, 1969-1970, 1992 (Box-folder 29:25)
  - Correspondence- Individuals- Andrew Young, 1971, 1976 (Box-folder 29:26)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1969 April-August (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1969 September-October (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1969 November-December (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1970 January-February (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1970 March (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1970 April-November (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1972 January-April (Box-folder 30:8)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1972 May (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1972 June-August (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1972 September-December (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1974 February-October (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1974 November-December (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1975 January-February (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1975 March (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1975 April-November (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Correspondence- Letters of Support, 1977 (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1969 (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1970 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1971 January-September (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1971 October-December (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1975-1976 June (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1976 July-December (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1977 January -March (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1977 April-May (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Correspondence- Media Requests, 1977 June-1978, 1982 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Correspondence- Request for Donation, 1969 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Correspondence- Request for Donation, 1971 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Correspondence- Request for Endorsements, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1968 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1969 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1970 January-May (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1970 June-December (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1971 January-August (Box-folder 33:12)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1971 September-October (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1972 February-August (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1972 September-October (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1973 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1974 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1975 (Box-folder 34:6)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1976 January-June (Box-folder 34:7)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1976 July-August (Box-folder 34:8)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1976 September-December (Box-folder 34:9)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1977 January-March (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1977 April-May (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Correspondence- Request for Legal Aid, 1977 June-November, 1985 (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1970 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1971 (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1972 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1973 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1974 (Box-folder 35:9)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1975 (Box-folder 35:10)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1976 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - Correspondence- Request for Military Aid, 1977 (Box-folder 35:12)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Griffin Bell Hearings, 1977 (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Black Business and Enterprises, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Correspondence- Colleges and Universities, 1971-2002 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning the Angela Davis Case, 1971 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning the Israel/Jewish Question, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 36:5)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Julian Bond: Black Rebel by John Neary, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Newsletter/Journal on Black Politics, 1969-1970 July (Box-folder 36:7)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Newsletter/Journal on Black Politics, 1970 August-1973, n.d (Box-folder 36:8)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Photographs of Julian Bond, 1969-1974, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 36:9)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning South Africa, 1977 (Box-folder 36:10)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Sterilization Controversy, 1973 (Box-folder 36:11)
  - Correspondence- Topical concerning Fletcher Thompson and a Job Corps Training Center for Atlanta, 1969 (Box-folder 36:12)
- Series III: Organizations
  - A Organizations, 1963-1976, 2004 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - The African-American Institute, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 37:2)